http://www.billyblue.com.au/privacy-policy

Torrens University Australia
BusinessTorrens University AustraliaChifley Business SchoolAPM College of Business and CommunicationReal Madrid Graduate SchoolDesignTorrens University AustraliaBilly Blue College of DesignMedia Design SchoolHealthTorrens University AustraliaHospitalityBlue Mountains International Hotel Management SchoolWilliam Blue College of Hospitality Management
BLOG|
LEARNING PORTAL|
MY TORRENS
Billy Blue College of Design
Talk to a Course Adviser1300 851 245
CONTACT US
HomeDesign CareersCoursesBranded Fashion Design CoursesDiploma Of Branded Fashion DesignBachelor of Branded Fashion DesignCommunication (Graphic) Design CoursesDiploma of Graphic DesignBachelor of Communication DesignDigital Media Design CoursesBachelor of 3D Design and AnimationDiploma of 3D Design and AnimationBachelor of UX and Web DesignDiploma of UX and Web DesignBachelor of Film and VideoDiploma of Film and Video Interior Design CoursesBachelor of Interior Design (Commercial)Bachelor of Interior Design (Residential)Diploma of Interior Design and DecorationDouble DegreesBachelor of Business and Bachelor of Design Photography CoursesDiploma of Photography and Photo ImagingPostgraduate CoursesMaster of Design / Master of Design (Advanced)Graduate Certificate in UX and Web DesignCREATIVE TECHNOLOGY COURSESBachelor Of Software Engineering (Artificial Intelligence)Bachelor of Game Design and DevelopmentBachelor Of Software Engineering (Game Programming)Graduate Certificate in Software EngineeringGraduate Certificate in Digital Transformation & Creative IntelligenceMaster Of Software Engineering (Artificial Intelligence, Advanced)Master Of Software Engineering (Cloud Computing, Advanced)Diploma of Software EngineeringDiploma of Game Design and DevelopmentGeneral Design CoursesDiploma of DesignShort Courses and Micro-credentialsLEAD DIGITAL CHANGEStudy OptionsStudy OnlinePhilosophyApplyKey datesAdmissions CriteriaTuition feesInternational StudentsScholarshipsPortfolio & Interview RequirementsApply nowDesign Short CoursesApplication for Course CreditBright AwardsLife At Billy BlueThe Story of Billy BlueMeet Our PeopleSenior ManagementStudent AwardsDesign InternshipsCampus LocationsStudy supportCounselling SupportStudent Representative CouncilInternational StudentsInternational ProspectusCollaborate with usDesign Industry PartnersInitiate A Design Project With UsBlog & Events Upcoming eventsSydney Upcoming EventsMelbourne Upcoming EventsBrisbane Upcoming EventsInteractive Online Workshops – Design ThinkingDesign & Creative Technology Course & Career WebinarBlogCurrent StudentsKey datesEvents for studentsCampus mapsGet StartedStudy support and English helpService HubI study at UltimoI study at BrisbaneI study at MelbourneInternational StudentsCourse GuideApply NowContact Us
Menu
HomeDesign CareersCourses
Branded Fashion Design CoursesDiploma Of Branded Fashion DesignBachelor of Branded Fashion DesignCommunication (Graphic) Design CoursesDiploma of Graphic DesignBachelor of Communication DesignDigital Media Design CoursesBachelor of 3D Design and AnimationDiploma of 3D Design and AnimationBachelor of UX and Web DesignDiploma of UX and Web DesignBachelor of Film and VideoDiploma of Film and Video Interior Design CoursesBachelor of Interior Design (Commercial)Bachelor of Interior Design (Residential)Diploma of Interior Design and DecorationDouble DegreesBachelor of Business and Bachelor of Design Photography CoursesDiploma of Photography and Photo ImagingPostgraduate CoursesMaster of Design / Master of Design (Advanced)Graduate Certificate in UX and Web DesignCREATIVE TECHNOLOGY COURSESBachelor Of Software Engineering (Artificial Intelligence)Bachelor of Game Design and DevelopmentBachelor Of Software Engineering (Game Programming)Graduate Certificate in Software EngineeringGraduate Certificate in Digital Transformation & Creative IntelligenceMaster Of Software Engineering (Artificial Intelligence, Advanced)Master Of Software Engineering (Cloud Computing, Advanced)Diploma of Software EngineeringDiploma of Game Design and DevelopmentGeneral Design CoursesDiploma of DesignShort Courses and Micro-credentialsStudy OptionsStudy Online
PhilosophyApply
Key datesAdmissions CriteriaTuition feesInternational StudentsScholarshipsPortfolio & Interview RequirementsApply nowDesign Short CoursesApplication for Course CreditBright Awards
Life At Billy Blue
The Story of Billy BlueMeet Our PeopleSenior ManagementStudent AwardsDesign InternshipsCampus LocationsStudy supportStudent Representative CouncilInternational StudentsInternational Prospectus
Collaborate with us
Design Industry PartnersInitiate A Design Project With Us
Blog & Events
Upcoming eventsSydney Upcoming EventsMelbourne Upcoming EventsBrisbane Upcoming EventsBlog
Current Students
Key datesEvents for studentsCampus mapsGet StartedStudy support and English helpService HubI study at UltimoI study at BrisbaneI study at MelbourneInternational Students
Course GuideApply NowContact Us
CONTACT US
CALL US
1300 851 245
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Billy Blue College of Design
Visitors to THINK websites
THINK uses cookies and measurement tools on our websites, as do third parties such as analytics, advertising or advertisement serving partners who may monitor unidentifiable statistics relating to website access and usage.
Read more
Purpose of collecting and holding personal information
THINK collects and holds personal information for the purpose of providing educational products and services and requests information to manage and administer those products and services.
Read more
Anonymity
THINK will provide individuals with the option of remaining anonymous or using a pseudonym in their dealings with THINK where it is lawful and practicable (for example, when making an enquiry).
Read more
Security of Information
THINK maintains personal information in paper-based and electronic records and systems.
Read more
Use and disclosure of personal information
THINK uses and discloses personal information for the purposes disclosed at the time of collection, or otherwise as set out in this Policy.
Read more
Direct Marketing
THINK uses and discloses the personal information it collects for direct marketing purposes. Individuals may contact THINK to request not to receive direct marketing communications.
Read more
Disclosure of information to overseas recipients
Unless consent has been given or an exception to the Australian privacy principles apply, Billy Blue College of Design will only disclose personal information to overseas recipients.
Read more
Access and Correction of Personal Information
For simple enquiries regarding personal information (such as confirming current contact details or confirming results) please contact the relevant Student Services team.
Read more >
Enquiries and Complaints
All privacy enquiries and complaints should be directed in writing to the Privacy Officer using the Request for Access to Personal Information form.
Read more
Privacy Policy in detail
Visitors to THINK websites
THINK uses cookies and measurement tools on our websites, as do third parties such as analytics, advertising or advertisement serving partners who may monitor unidentifiable statistics relating to website access and usage. THINK uses and discloses the unidentifiable information collected through the use of cookies and measurement tools in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This includes using the information to report statistics, analyse trends, diagnose problems and improve the quality of THINK’s products and services.
THINK may combine our cookies and information (collected through the cookies and measurement tools) on the THINK websites with other information (including information collected by third parties using their own cookies and measurement tools) to provide better or more relevant services and information.
If an individual does not want information collected through the use of cookies and/or measurement tools, they may be able to delete or reject cookies and/or some of the measurement software features through their browser or the settings section of their mobile or tablet device. Disabling these features may cause some of the functions on the THINK websites to work less effectively.
THINK provides links to external websites, as well as to third party websites that allow interaction and sharing of content including social media buttons such as Facebook share, Twitter, Pinterest and Google+. These linked sites, applications and widgets are not under THINK’s control and THINK does not accept responsibility for the conduct of companies linked to THINK websites, or their collection of information through these third party applications or widgets. Before disclosing information on any other website, or using these applications or widgets users are advised to examine the terms and conditions of using that website and the relevant third party’s data collection practices and privacy policy. The Internet is not always a secure method of transmitting information. While THINK takes reasonable steps to ensure all information it receives is maintained securely, THINK cannot ensure that communications conducted via the Internet will be secure.
Purpose of collecting and holding personal information
THINK collects and holds personal information for the purpose of providing educational products and services and requests information to manage and administer those products and services. When THINK collects personal information about individuals who are not students, THINK generally does so for the purposes for which the information was provided. All appropriate personal information will be held by THINK to satisfy record-keeping obligations.
Anonymity
THINK will provide individuals with the option of remaining anonymous or using a pseudonym in their dealings with THINK where it is lawful and practicable (for example, when making an enquiry). Generally is it not practicable or lawful for THINK to deal with individuals anonymously or pseudonymously on an ongoing basis (for example, if the individual wishes to enrol in a course of study).
Security of Information
THINK maintains personal information in paper-based and electronic records and systems. Personal information may be collected in paper-based documents and converted to electronic form for storage (with the paper-based document either being archived or securely destroyed). Archived records are stored at an external storage facility in Australia and information held in electronic form is generally held on servers controlled by THINK in Australia. THINK uses physical security, password protection and other measures to ensure that all personal information is protected from misuse, interference and loss; and from unauthorised access, modification and disclosure.
Use and disclosure of personal information
THINK uses and discloses personal information for the purposes disclosed at the time of collection, or otherwise as set out in this Policy. Personal information will not be used or disclosed for any other purposes, unless consent has been given or THINK is authorised or required to do so by law.
Personal information will generally only be used or disclosed as follows:
To provide the products, services or information requested from THINK (including enrolment, assessment and issuing certificates of completion and testamurs).
Personal information may also be disclosed to third parties (where applicable) to assist THINK with functions such as recruitment of students, work integrated learning placements or providing overseas student health cover
To register and administer events, promotions or competitions
To verify personal information details upon request from third parties, such as completion of courses, a request from a potential employer verifying a qualification and further enrolment into another institution
To comply with THINK’s legal and regulatory obligations, including disclosure and reporting to Commonwealth, State and Territory government agencies for planning, evaluative, administrative and funding purposes. This may include:
disclosure and reporting to Commonwealth and State government agencies (including State Training Authorities) for the purpose of administrating entitlements to financial assistance under Commonwealth and State government programs for supporting students, such as FEE-HELP and VET FEE-HELP
disclosure to government agencies responsible for administrating and regulating education and training providers in Australia, such as Tertiary Education Quality and Standards Agency (TEQSA), Australian Skills Quality Authority (ASQA), Tuition Protection Service (TPS), and
disclosure to government agencies with responsibility for administering immigration and student visa arrangements (including disclosure of suspected breaches of student visa conditions)
For students under 18, information regarding attendance, progress and general well-being may be provided in order to keep parent(s) and/or guardian(s) adequately informed
To assist THINK to make its sites, service and products more accessible and valuable to students
To perform various administrative or management functions including administering billing and debt recovery; training of staff and contractors and managing their work performance and career progression, quality assurance and evaluation; maintenance and testing of information technology systems; obtaining advice from consultants and professional advisers; management of legal liabilities and claims (including liaising with legal representatives and insurers)
Direct Marketing
THINK uses and discloses the personal information it collects for direct marketing purposes.
Individuals may contact THINK to request not to receive direct marketing communications. Direct marketing may include providing individuals with information regarding products, services and new developments. If an individual does not wish to receive marketing material, please note THINK will still contact them in relation to the ongoing relationship. For example, THINK will still send individuals invoices and information that are relevant to their course of study.
Disclosure of information to overseas recipients
Unless consent has been given or an exception to the Australian privacy principles apply, Billy Blue College of Design will only disclose personal information to overseas recipients where reasonable steps have been taken to ensure the overseas recipient does not breach the Australian Privacy Principles in relation to your personal information.
Access and Correction of Personal Information
For simple enquiries regarding personal information (such as confirming current contact details or confirming results) please contact the relevant Student Services team. To request access to personal information, please contact THINK’s designated Privacy Officer at privacy@think.edu.au. In limited circumstances, access to personal information may be declined in accordance with the Australian Privacy Principles.
THINK endeavours to keep all personal information accurate, up-to-date and complete; however, if information held by THINK is considered to be inaccurate, out-of-date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading, a request can be made for a correction of the information. Please contact THINK’s designated Privacy Officer at privacy@think.edu.au. After receiving such a request, THINK will take reasonable steps to correct the information.
A request to remove or delete personal information may not be possible to comply with where the personal information must be retained by THINK for a period specified by applicable legislative and regulatory requirements. THINK may refuse a request to access, correct or delete personal information in certain circumstances. In such instances, THINK will provide a reason for the decision.
Enquiries and Complaints
All privacy enquiries and complaints should be directed in writing to the Privacy Officer using the Request for Access to Personal Information form. THINK will respond to a complaint within a reasonable period of time. The contact details for THINK are:
Privacy Officer Think Education Group
Level 7, 80 Pacific Highway Sydney NSW 3060 www.think.edu.auprivacy@think.edu.au If THINK’s response to a complaint is unsatisfactory or it is believed that THINK may have breached the Australian Privacy Principles or the Privacy Act, a complaint can be made to the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner. The Office of the Australian Information Commissioner can be contacted by telephone on 1300 363 992. Full contact details for the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner can be found online at www.oaic.gov.au.
Torrens University Australia
Billy Blue College of Design courses are delivered by Torrens University Australia Ltd,
ABN 99 154 937 005, RTO 41343, CRICOS 03389E. | Privacy Policy
TORRENS UNIVERSITY LANGUAGE CENTRE (TULC)
Real Madrid Graduate School
